http://www.iafd.com/privacy.asp

privacy info
This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for the Internet Adult Film Database (IAFD) http://www.iafd.com.
Information Collection and Use
IAFD is the sole owner of the information collected on this site.
We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user.
Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site.
If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site.
The only drawback to this is that the user's preference settings will not be maintained.
Log Files
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.
IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. We track page counts per IP address and reserve the right to limit traffic based on high usage (currently over 2500 pages per day).
Sharing
We have a relationship with Quantserv which aggregates anonymized visitor information which is made available to our advertisers.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we [IAFD] are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.
We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.
This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
Security
This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information.
So much so, we have chosen to
not collect any information at all.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email.
Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
Contact Information
If you have any questions or concerns, please contact us at iafd@iafd.com
This privacy statement is based on the work of the late, great Truste Privacy Wizard
